Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- City College of New York - New York, NY
  - Gymnasium - electric work, running track floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1905-07-25 (Box 377)
  - Gymnasium - electric work, roof plan; blueprint on paper (Box 377)
  - Main Building - electric work, cellar plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-4)
  - Main Building - electric work, ground floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-4)
  - Main Building - electric work, 1st floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-4)
  - Main Building - electric work, 2nd floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-4)
  - Main Building - electric work, 3rd floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-4)
  - Main Building - electric work, 4th floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-5)
  - Main Building - electric work, 5th floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-5)
  - Main Building - electric work, upper story plans of main tower; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1905-07-25 (Box OS-5)
  - All buildings - electric work, ground plan, feeder schedule; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1905-02-20 (Box OS-5)
  - All buildings - electric work, schedule of distribution boxes & feeder sheet; [?] print on linen, 1905-05-10 (Box OS-5)
  - Main Building - details of room #2, 5th floor; ink on linen (damaged) (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - large gables, staircase; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-02-20 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - interior detail for museum, 3rd & 4th fl.; ink on linen (damaged) (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - interior details of executive offices, 1st floor main tower; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-02-20 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - details of staircases etc. adjoining central tower; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-02-20 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - arches for organs in towers; ink on linen (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - detail of approaches, campus entrances; ink on linen (damaged) (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - sections; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - electric work: 4th floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - electric work: 5th floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - electric work: 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - electric work: 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - electric work: cellar floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - electric work: ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box OS-6)
  - Main Building - details of upper part of main tower; ink on linen, 1904-11-01 (Box OS-6)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - assembly hall, emblems for windows; blueprint on paper (17 sheets) (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - assembly hall, sketches for stained glass; blueprint on paper, 1905-11-24 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - Dept. of Chemistry, furniture & equipment; graphite on trace (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - Dept. of Physics, furniture & equipment; graphite on trace (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - Dept. of Natural History, furniture & equipment; graphite on trace (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - Dept. of Chemistry, furniture & equipment; graphite on trace (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - furniture & equipment, numbering of tables & cases in rooms 6-8, 1st & 2nd fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-05-10 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - lunch counter partition; graphite on trace, 1906-08-07 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - Natural History, laboratories; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - bearing for benches in assembly hall; graphite on trace, 1907-04-23 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - details of rack C #183; graphite on trace, 1907-08-30 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - assembly hall benches & location; graphite on trace, 1906-11-20 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - door plates & rings, Amsterdam Ave. entrance; graphite on trace, 1906-02-26 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - Dept. of Chemistry, detail of case C #192; graphite on trace, 1906-05-22 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - campus entrance, door plates & rings; graphite on trace, 1906-02-26 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - plans of rooms, blackboards; graphite on trace, 1905-11-23 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - letters on directory bulletin board; graphite on trace, 1906-11-20 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - assembly hall, sketches for stained glass; graphite on trace, manila backing, 1905-11-24 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - change of 3rd fl. windows, small gables; ink on linen, 1903-06-25 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - strain diagrams of roof trusses; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section, S to N thro' east wing; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - schedule for steel columns & struts, cast iron col. bases; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section, S to N thro' towers; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - iron detail, bay window campus elevation; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section E to W thro' south wing; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing of mansard roof at large dormers in wings; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - sections of mansard roof in wings; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - structural details, center portion of bldg; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - 3rd story gallery cantilevers; ink on linen, 1904-04-14 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - change to recess in side cables of central pavilion, Amsterdam Ave.; ink on linen (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - supports for house tank; ink on linen, 1905-01-20 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - advance sheet of framing for removable panel at ceiling; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-01-14 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - brick arch (with 4" reveal) to inside of outside arch, campus entrance; graphite on trace (damaged), 1904-06-04 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - tower clock (exterior); graphite on trace, 1905-07-11 (Box 370)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - 4th floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - roof plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - cellar floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing: roof plan or G tier; ink on linen, 1904-12-28 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing: F tier or 4th floor; ink on linen, 1904-10-04 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing: E tier or 3rd floor; ink on linen, 1904-05-05 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing: D tier or 2nd floor; ink on linen, 1904-04-30 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing: C tier or 1st floor; ink on linen, 1904-04-17 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing: B tier or ground floor; ink on linen, 1904-04-07 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: special connections for fittings, 1st-4th stories; ink on linen (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: roof plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: 4th floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - electric work: cellar plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - Amsterdam Ave. elevation; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - 138th St. elevation; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - sections a-a & b-b; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - side elevation of central pavilion; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section d-d; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section e-e; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - campus elevation; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing for dormer window; ink on linen, 1904-07-20 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing for dormer windows; ink on linen, 1904-07-25 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - roof purlin plan; ink on linen, 1904-07-21 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - trusses over assembly hall; ink on linen, 1904-07-28 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - truss over assembly hall T1; ink on linen, 1904-07-06 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - stage framing, D tier; ink on linen, 1904-05-17 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - gallery girders, 3rd fl.; ink on linen, 1904-05-05 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - bay window framing; ink on linen, 1904-04-26 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - column schedule; ink on linen, 1904-04-05 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing: ridges; ink on linen, 1904-09-28 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - gallery plan or E tier; ink on linen, 1904-05-04 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - BM tier or mezzanine; ink on linen, 1904-04-26 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - door bucks; ink on linen, 1904-12-30 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - partition lintels; ink on linen, 1904-12-31 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - partition lintels; ink on linen, 1904-12-30 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - dormers; ink on linen, 1904-08-12 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - purlin plan, tower roof; ink on linen, 1904-08-11 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - tower trusses; ink on linen, 1904-08-01 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - roof purlin plan; ink on linen, 1904-08-11 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - roof purlin plan; ink on linen, 1904-08-08 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - purlin plan panel L & framing for dormer DE; ink on linen, 1904-07-27 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - roof purlin plan; ink on linen, 1904-07-16 (Box 370-A)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - strain diagrams for roof trusses; blueprint on paper, 1904-04-14 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - cellar floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1904-11-01 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - roof plan; blueprint on paper, 1904-11-01 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - sections a-a & b-b; blueprint on paper, 1904-11-01 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - side elevation of central pavilion; blueprint on paper, 1904-11-01 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section e-e; blueprint on paper, 1904-11-01 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section d-d; blueprint on paper, 1904-11-01 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - staircase from 1st floor to assembly hall platform; blueprint on paper, 1905-02-14 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - 3rd story cantilevers; blueprint on paper (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - specification for alterations; ink on paper (20 pages), 1920-01-15 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - steel framing details: columns, skylight curb, etc.; ink on paper (35 sheets), 1904 (Box 370-B)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - sections of mansard roof in wings; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-14 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - schedule for steel columns & struts and cast iron bases; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-14 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section through towers; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-14 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - section through south wing; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-14 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - framing of mansard roof at large dormers in wings; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-14 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - iron detail, bay window campus elevation; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-14 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - detail of dormer windows; aniline on paper (damaged) (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - structural details of center portion of building; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-14 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - structural details of platform & gallery in assembly; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-04-28 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - interior details, except assembly hall; aniline on paper (folded, damaged), 1904-11-01 (Box 370-C)
  - Sub-Freshman Building - interior detail of assembly hall; aniline on paper (damaged), 1905-03-20 (Box 370-C)
  - Chemical Building - terra cotta details; blueprint on paper (2 sheets), 1904-05-31 (Box 370-B)
- Cleveland Trust Company - Cleveland, OH
  - Alteration - foundation plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-09-30 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 9th floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: typical floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 9th floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 1st floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 2nd floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 3rd floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 4th floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 5th floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 6th floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-10-01 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 7th floor framing; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: typical floor; blueprint on paper, 1919-10-01 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: typical floors; blueprint on paper, 1919-10-07 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: typical floors; blueprint & crayon on paper, 1919-09-03 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 5th floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper, 1919-09-12 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 4th floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper, 1919-09-18 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 3rd floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper, 1919-09-18 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 2nd floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 1st floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper, 1919-09-18 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 9th floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: typical floor plan; blueprint & crayon on paper, 1919-09-03 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - basement plan showing footing; blueprint on paper, 1919-10-06 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - typical floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - 6th floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-09-11 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - 7th floor plan; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - 8th floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-08-08 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - foundation plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-10-02 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - safe deposit dept.; blueprint on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: foundation plan [?]; ink on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: typical floors; ink & graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 9th floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 1st floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 2nd floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 3rd floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 4th floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 5th floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: unidentified; ink & graphite on paper (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 9th floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: typical floor; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: roof framing plan; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 6th floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 7th floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing: 8th floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - foundation plan; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - column schedule; graphite on trace, 2 sheets, 1919-10-08 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - structural diagram for 20 story building; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - section; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - wind stresses; graphite on trace, 1919-09-23 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - structural diagram for 20 story building; graphite & crayon on trace, 1919-10-02 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - structural diagram for 20 story building, scheme B; graphite & crayon on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - structural diagram for 20 story building; graphite & crayon on trace, 1919-10-02 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - basement plan; graphite & crayon on trace, 1919-10-06 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - structural diagram; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - 16 story structural diagram; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - foundation details; graphite on trace, 1919-08-28 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - 16 story foundation diagram; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - 20 story structural diagram, schemes A & B; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - typical floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-26 (Box 336)
  - Alteration - framing detail; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - 20 story structural diagram; graphite on trace (Box 336)
  - Alteration - basement plan; blueprint on paper (Box 334)
  - Alteration - typical floor plan of 16 story building; blueprint & crayon on paper, 1919-08-20 (Box 334)
  - Alteration - typical floor plan of 16 story building; blueprint & crayon on paper (Box 334)
  - Alteration - typical floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-08-26 (Box 334)
  - Alteration - foundation plan; blueprint on paper, 2 pieces (Box 334)
  - Alteration - study for Euclid Ave elevation; blueprint on paper, 1919-08-27 (Box 334)
  - Alteration - study for East 9th St elevation; blueprint on paper, 1919-08-27 (Box 334)
  - 1st floor beams; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - Sections of store building; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - System of drainage; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - Foundation plan; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - Basement floor beams, column schedule & flue; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - 3rd floor beams; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - Roof beams (bank bldg) & 5th floor beams (store bldg); ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - Column centre plan; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - Roof plan; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - 4th floor beams; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - 2nd floor beams; ink on linen (Box OS-9)
  - 2nd floor plan; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - Erie Street elevations; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - Erie Street elevation of store building; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - 4th floor plan; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - South & east elevations of store bldg; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - Details of dome; ink on linen, 1906-04-14 (Box 334)
  - 1st floor plan; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - 5th floor plan; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - Basement plan; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - 3rd floor plan; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - East & south elevations; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - Cellar plan of store building; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - Detail of fresh air intake; ink on linen (Box 334)
  - Beams in 1st floor under vestibule of Holler vault; ink on linen, 1906-11-28 (Box 334)
  - Addition - column load sheets (51); printed ink on paper, 1919 (Box 334)
  - 5th floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 336-A)
  - 4th floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 336-A)
  - 3rd floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 336-A)
  - 2nd floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 336-A)
  - 1st floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - passenger elevators; blueprint on paper, 1919-11-11 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - East 9th St elevation study; blueprint on paper, 1919-09-15 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - Euclid Ave. elevation study; blueprint on paper, 1919-08-27 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 1st floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - basement plan; blueprint on paper, 1919-10-07 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - basement plan, scheme A; blueprint on paper, 1919-10-09 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - reflector to illuminate sign; blueprint on paper, 1917-02-07 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - bronze sign; blueprint on paper (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - Euclid Ave floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 1st floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-26 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - corner entrance floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 2nd floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - study for Euclid Ave. elevation; graphite on trace, 1919-08-27 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - study for East 9th St. elevation; graphite on trace, 1919-08-27 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - section; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 8th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-08 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 7th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-08 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 6th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-08 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - typical floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-08 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - basement floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-15 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 1st floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-12 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 2nd floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-12 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 3rd floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-12 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 4th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-08-12 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - basement plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 5th floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 7th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 6th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 5th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 1st floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - typical floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 3rd floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - mezzanine or 2nd floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - basement plan; graphite on trace, 1919-10-07 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 8th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - basement plan; graphite on trace, 1919-10-09 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 4th floor plan; graphite on trace, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - construction of illuminated letters for sign; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - bronze illuminated sign; graphite on trace (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - detail of bronze illuminated sign; graphite on trace, 1916-06-16 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 1st floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - mezzanine or 2nd floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 3rd floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-25 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 4th floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-03 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 5th floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 6th floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 7th floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-30 (Box 336-A)
  - Alteration - 8th floor plan; hectograph on paper, 1919-09-03 (Box 336-A)